&gt;&gt; I'm now here with Arpan Chakraborty who is one of our Udacity computer vision
— 今天 我们请来了 Arpan Chakraborty
experts.
他是优达学城的计算机视觉专家
And Drew Gray, who is the director of engineering at Otto,
还有 Drew Gray 他是 Otto 的工程主管
which is now part of Uber.
Otto 现在隶属于 Uber
So guys, in the end of this lesson, students are going to
在本模块最后
implement a pipeline to detect and track vehicles in a video stream.
学员将使用一系列流水化的程序 来检测和跟踪视频中的车辆
So Drew, maybe you could tell us a little bit more about the role of
Drew 你能否给大家讲讲
vehicle detection and tracking in the self-driving cars that you work on.
在你的无人驾驶项目中 车辆检测和跟踪所扮演的角色？
&gt;&gt; Sure.
— 没问题
Knowing where the other vehicles are on the road and being able to anticipate
知道其他车辆在公路上的位置
where they're heading next is essential in a self-driving car.
并能预测它们下一步的行驶方向 对于无人驾驶车是至关重要的
At Otto, we're writing software that allows the car to recognize other
在 Otto 我们开发用于
vehicles on the road.
识别公路上的其他车辆的软件
And determine things like how far away they are, which way they're going, and
并确定汽车的距离、行驶方向以及
how fast they're moving.
行驶速度
Much the same way as we do with our own eyes as we drive.
这和人类驾驶时通过眼睛观察非常类似
&gt;&gt; Very cool.
— 太酷了
Object detection and tracking is a central theme in computer vision.
目标检测和跟踪是计算机视觉的一个中心主题
And in this lesson you'll be using what you might call traditional computer
本节课中 你将使用所谓的
vision techniques to tackle this problem.
传统计算机视觉技术来解决这个问题
You'll first explore what kind of visual features you can extract from images
你首先要研究 从图片中提取哪些视觉特征
in order to reliably classify vehicles.
才能实现稳定的车辆分类
Next, you'll look into searching an image for detections.
接下去 你将学习在一张图像中进行目标检测
And then you'll track those detections from frame to frame in a video stream.
最后 你需要在视频中逐帧跟踪这些检测到的物体
&gt;&gt; Awesome.
— 太好了
So Drew, I know you've got a background in both the sort of traditional computer
Drew 我知道你在传统计算机视觉方面
vision techniques.
有所研究
&gt;&gt; Mm-hm.
— 没错
&gt;&gt; As well as using deep learning for computer vision.
- 你同时对深度学习在计算机视觉上的应用也很熟悉
So maybe you could tell us why it's useful to study both approaches.
能否讲一下 为什么这两种方法都需要学习呢
&gt;&gt; Sure.
— 好的
With traditional computer vision approaches
采用传统计算机视觉技术
you basically tune all the parameters by hand.
你需要手动调整所有参数
Which gives you a lot of intuition about what works and why.
这可以让你直观理解哪些设置是起作用的 以及为什么起作用
When it comes to things like image classification.
但涉及到图像分类等任务时
In many cases a deep learning approach works even better for the same tasks.
在很多情况下 对于同一个任务 深度学习的效果更好
But can seem like kind of a black box.
不过深度学习就像一个黑盒子
We're not quite sure why it works.
我们不太清楚其工作原理
By learning both approaches,
通过学习两种方法
you can gain maximum insight and get the best performance in your algorithms.
你可以深入了解算法 并让算法发挥出最佳性能
&gt;&gt; Cool.
— 好极了
Well let's get started.
那么 我们开始吧